Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1962-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1981
  - I-66 (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - I-66 (Folder 6, Box 24)
  - I-66 (Folder 7, Box 24)
  - TRANSPORTATION - ISSUE PAPER #8. (Folder 8, Box 24)
  - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66 INFORMATION. (Folder 9, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66. (Folder 10, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66. (Folder 11, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66. (Folder 12, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS I-66. (Folder 13, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE DECEMBER TO MAY). (Folder 14, Box 24)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA) PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE APRIL TO JANUARY). (Folder 15, Box 24)
  - POTOMAC RIVER BILL (CORRESPONDENCE -1979). (Folder 1, Box 25)
  - POTOMAC RIVER BILL (CORRESPONDENCE -1979). (Folder 2, Box 25)
  - POTOMAC RIVER BILL (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1979 TO 1977). (Folder 3, Box 25)
  - POTOMAC RIVER BILL (CORRESPONDENCE - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR POTOMAC RIVER BILL (DECEMBER 7, 1976). (Folder 5, Box 25)
  - 1975 - INTERIOR COMMITTEE RE: POTOMAC RIVER. (Folder 6, Box 25)
  - 1977 - VIRGINIA WATER ISSUES. (Folder 7, Box 25)
  - VIRGINIA RE: AQUEDUCT AND ARLINGTON. (Folder 8, Box 25)
  - AQUEDUCT BILL. (Folder 9, Box 25)
  - VIRGINIA METRO (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 10, Box 25)
  - METRO (PRESS AND CLIPPINGS -1980 TO 1975). (Folder 11, Box 25)
  - (VIRGINIA) METRO FINANCING (GENERAL - 1977). (Folder 12, Box 25)
  - 1978 - VIRGINIA RE: METRO. (Folder 13, Box 25)
  - (VIRGINIA) METRO FINANCING (GENERAL - 1976 TO 1975). (Folder 14, Box 25)
  - (VIRGINIA) AIRPORT POLICY (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 15, Box 25)
  - (VIRGINIA) DULLES AIRPORT SAFETY (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 16, Box 25)
  - AIRPORTS. (Folder 17, Box 25)
  - AIRPORTS. (Folder 18, Box 25)
  - 1977 - VIRGINIA RE: TAXATION AT NATIONAL AIRPORT. (Folder 19, Box 25)
  - 1977 VIRGINIA LOCAL AIRPORTS. (Folder 20, Box 25)
  - 1979 - VIRGINIA RE: DULLES. (Folder 21, Box 25)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES MASTER PLAN (CORRESPONDENCE - 1978 TO 1976). (Folder 22, Box 25)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (CORRESPONDENCE - 1980 TO 1978). (Folder 1, Box 26)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (COVER LETTER JULY 12, 1979). (Folder 2, Box 26)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (CORRESPONDENCE - 1978 TO 1977). (Folder 3, Box 26)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1978 TO 1975) (Folder 4, Box 26)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (COVER LETTER - JULY 21, 1977). (Folder 5, Box 25)
  - VIRGINIA DULLES ACCESS ROAD (CORRESPONDENCE - 1976 TO 1975) (Folder 6, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - 1977 TO 1976). (Folder 7, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 8, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 9, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION SSI INFORMATION. (Folder 10, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - MARCH 1976 TO JANUARY 1975). (Folder 11, Box 26)
  - 1976- (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - DECEMBER TO APRIL, 1976). (Folder 12, Box 26)
  - 1976- (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - JULY TO MAY). (Folder 13, Box 26)
  - 1975 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - APRIL TO JANUARY). (Folder 14, Box 26)
  - 1977 - (VIRGINIA PUBLIC WORKS AND TRANSPORTATION (CORRESPONDENCE - DECEMBER TO SEPTEMBER). (Folder 15, Box 26)
  - VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - 1980). (Folder 1, Box 27)
  - VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - 1979 TO 1978). (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - 1979 TO 1978). (Folder 3, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - NOVEMBER TO AUGUST). (Folder 4, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - JUNE). (Folder 5, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - MAY TO JANUARY). (Folder 6, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (COVER LETTER - APRIL 26, 1978). (Folder 7, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 8, Box 27)
  - 1977 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (GENERAL). (Folder 9, Box 27)
  - 1977 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE INFORMATION (GENERAL). (Folder 10, Box 27)
  - 1978 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - 1977 TO 1976). (Folder 11, Box 27)
  - 1976 VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE). (Folder 12, Box 27)
  - VIRGINIA AIRPORT NOISE AND ADVISORY (CORRESPONDENCE - 1975). (Folder 13, Box 27)
  - 1976 - D.C. COMMITTEE COMMUTER TAX (CORRESPONDENCE - 1978 TO 1975). (Folder 1, Box 28)
  - VIRGINIA ARLINGTON HOUSING (GENERAL - 1977 TO 1975). (Folder 2, Box 28)
  - VIRGINIA (GENERAL - 1977 TO 1975). (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - FAIRFAX - FALLS CHURCH (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1976). (Folder 4, Box 28)
  - VEPCO (GENERAL - 1975). (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - VIRGINIA IMPACT AID (CORRESPONDENCE 1980 TO 1977). (Folder 6, Box 28)
  - (VIRGINIA) GYPSY MOTH AND BEMILIN. (Folder 7, Box 28)
  - 1979 - SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY VIRGINIA SURVEY PLANTS (GENERAL). (Folder 8, Box 28)
  - 1979 - VIRGINIA SHORT HILL. (GENERAL). (Folder 9, Box 28)
  - 1979 - VIRGINIA IN - LIEU - TAXES - FOREIGN PROPERTY (GENERAL). (Folder 10, Box 28)
  - ARLINGTON (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1979 TO 1974). (Folder 11, Box 28)
  - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1979 TO 1975). (Folder 12, Box 28)
  - LANDOW ISSUES. (Folder 13, Box 28)
  - (VIRGINIA) SAFE DRINKING WATER (GENERAL - 1980). (Folder 14, Box 28)
  - (VIRGINIA) COLONIAL VILLAGE. (Folder 15, Box 28)
  - DAVIS - BACON ACT (LABOR). (Folder 16, Box 28)
  - CURRENT BOTTLE DEPOSIT BILL (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1979). (Folder 17, Box 28)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1980. (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - GUT ISSUES (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1978). (Folder 2, Box 29)
  - CASEWORK STATISTICS (CHARTS - 1980 TO 1978). (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - CASEWORK STATISTICS (GENERAL - 1980 TO 1977). (Folder 4, Box 29)
  - CASEWORK STATISTICS (CHARTS - 1980 TO 1975). (Folder 5, Box 29)
  - TOWN MEETINGS (1980 - 1975). (Folder 6, Box 29)
  - TENTH DISTRICT LEGISLATION (PRESS RELEASES 1980 TO 1975). (Folder 7, Box 29)
  - JLF SPEECHES #2. (Folder 8, Box 29)
  - JLF SPEECHES #1. (Folder 9, Box 29)
  - METRO CAUCUS (PRESS RELEASES, CLIPPINGS - 1979 TO 1975). (Folder 10, Box 29)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1979). (Folder 11, Box 29)
  - NEWS LETTERS - COMPLETE FILE (1979 - 1975). (Folder 12, Box 29)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1978. (Folder 13, Box 29)
  - CARTER MEETING (CLIPPINGS - 1978). (Folder 14, Box 29)
  - JLF SCHEDULE 1978 - 1977. (Folder 15, Box 29)
  - TED TAYLOR FILE (GENERAL - 1977). (Folder 16, Box 29)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1977. (Folder 17, Box 29)
  - NEWSLETTER - DEMO COMMITTEES (GENERAL - 1977 TO 1975). (Folder 18, Box 29)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR INFORMATION (DECEMBER, 1976). (Folder 19, Box 29)
  - CAMPAIGN 1976 (PRESS RELEASES). (Folder 20, Box 29)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1975. (Folder 21, Box 29)
  - PRESS CONFERENCE (1976 - 1975). (Folder 22, Box 29)
  - PRESS RELEASES - 1976. (Folder 23, Box 29)
  - NEWS BRIEFS - 1975. (Folder 24, Box 29)
  - 94th CONGRESS (GENERAL 1975). (Folder 25, Box 29)
  - POST ELECTION 1974 - 94th CAUCUS, ETC (NOVEMBER - DECEMBER). (Folder 26, Box 29)
  - JLF TRIP (CLIPS). (Folder 27, Box 29)
  - DSG 94th RECORDED VOTES 1ST SESSION. (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - DSG 94th 2nd SESSION. (Folder 2, Box 30)
  - DSG 95th 1st SESSION. (Folder 3, Box 30)
  - DSG 2nd SESSION. (Folder 4, Box 30)
  - DSG 96th CONGRESS 1st SESSION (Folder 5, Box 30)